internwise.co.uk 2018-01-22

# Privacy Policy | Internwise.co.uk

Kape Strategy Ltd (a UK registered company) is committed to protecting your privacy. Please take a moment to read and learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the Internwise website (the “Website”), submitting information or using any of our services, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

1 Information Collected

When you register as a member and set up a profile certain information is required. This includes personally identifiable information such as your name and email address. This information is stored on our systems.

2 Updating Your Information

You can freely update all of your personal information including email address, location, password and all profile details. We encourage you to keep your details up to date, as well as your CV.

3 Your Password

It is vital that you keep your password safe to prevent unauthorised access to your personal information. If you believe that your password has been compromised for any reason please change it immediately.

4 Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive that allows us to recognise your computer from one page access to the next. We use only session cookies which are designed not to be permanent or persistent. The session cookie is designed so that, once you close your browser, the cookie will simply terminate. If you configure your browser to reject cookies, you may still use some, but not all, portions of our site. For example, the login process and all member functionality requires that your browser accept cookies. We recommend closing browsers on shared computers after use.

5 Deleting Your Information

You have the option to delete your profile. Please note that this permanently deletes all your information. No data will remain on our systems with the exception of personal correspondence or support inquiries sent to us, which may be stored on file.

6 Personal Correspondence

Correspondence sent to us including emails and letters will be stored on file with access limited to our authorised staff members.

7 Disclosure of Your Information

7.1 By default, your public profile will be visible to the agencies or companies registered in our website. If you do not wish to be contacted and want to make your profile invisible, please visit your privacy settings at <http://www.internwise.co.uk/index.php?m=account_privacy> and select the option "Private Profile". Your profile will no longer be visible.  
7.2 We will not supply any member's details to any other member - please don't even ask us.  
7.3 We will not sell or rent or give your information to any third party.  
7.4 We will only disclose your information if legally obligated to do so by a statutory authority with the appropriate jurisdiction.

8 No Spam Policy

No Spam, not now, not ever! You will receive emails from us and you may receive anonymous emails from other members. However, we will never supply, sell or rent your email address to any third party.

9 Internal Use of Information

We may internally use your information to improve our services, analyse site usage, optimise content, etc. This will only be conducted by authorised staff members. We may use personally identifiable information to troubleshoot problems and implement our terms and conditions.

10 Refer a Friend Service

Our site includes an 'refer a friend' service. Your friends will never receive unsolicited email from us and, once your email is sent, they will never hear from us again unless they choose to become members themselves. You may not use the 'invite friends' services to send spam.

11 Security

Our technical team do their best to ensure the security of our systems. Internet Security is a complex topic and no system can be considered 100% secure. Should a security breach occur we would endeavour to react as fast as possible to remedy the problem. However we cannot assume responsibility for member details compromised in the unlikely event of a security breach.

12 Changes to This Policy

If we make material changes to our privacy policy, these changes will be posted to our privacy policy page. You should review this page regularly for updates.
